femina.com 2014-07-02

# FeMiNa

### The @Cybergrrl  
Privacy Statement

When you register for Cybergrrl.com: you will be required to provide Cybergrrl with the following information: your name, email address, zip code, gender, age, member name and password. In addition, you may choose to provide Cybergrrl with additional information, including: your address, household income, education, marital status and employment status. 

Cybergrrl will not sell or reveal to any third party your name, address, email address and member name, unless you provide your informed consent, except to the extent necessary to comply with applicable laws, police investigations, or in legal proceedings where such information is relevant. Cybergrrl allows access to database information by third-parties providing technical services, such as email, but only to the extent necessary to provide you with those services. In those instances, the third party is bound by these terms. Your informed consent shall be in the form of an "opt in" or similar policy. You understand and agree that Cybergrrl may disclose to third parties your zip code, gender and/or age, but only in the form of aggregated information. 

**About IP Addresses**   
Cybergrrl collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. 

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers -- the big computers that "serve" up Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address. 

When users request pages from Cybergrrl sites, our servers log the users' IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. 

**How CYBERGRRL Sites Do Not Use Cookies**   
CYBERGRRL sites never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Except as described below, CYBERGRRL sites do not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever. 

CYBERGRRL sites do not use cookies to identify specific individuals, except in such cases as online shopping and contest registration (where a cookie allows you to enter a contest every day without registering again each time). 

You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. CYBERGRRL does not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to the CYBERGRRL cookies policy. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the site, such as the shopping, contest, and game areas, will not function properly if you do so. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
Users should be aware that when they are on CYBERGRRL sites they could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from CYBERGRRL sites that take you outside our service. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement or a CYBERGRRL search result, the click takes you off the CYBERGRRL site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use CYBERGRRL's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online -- for example, via message boards or chat -- that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While CYBERGRRL strives to protect its users' personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. 

**Security Policy**  

The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our users is of utmost concern to us. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.   
We have significant security measures in place in our physical facilities and in our computer systems, databases, and communications networks to strictly protect information contained within our systems from loss, misuse or alteration. 

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using this site, you signify your assent to the CYBERGRRL Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. If you have any questions or concerns about Cybergrrl privacy protections as they relate to you, please email Femina.
